<Tasks>
    <GetItem>
        <ItemId Value="2949132830"/>
        <!-- Can be found in the URL of your workshop item -->
    </GetItem>
    <UpdateItem>
        <ModuleFolder Value="F:\Program Files (x86)\Steam\steamapps\common\Mount &amp; Blade II Bannerlord\Modules\PeasantRevenge"/>
        <!-- A direct path of your module -->   
        <ChangeNotes Value="
 - Changed notable exclude from revenge traits, so now only 60% (10% previous value) of the villages will be able to revenge at the begining of the game (see peasantRevengerExcludeTrait) 
 - Player can persuade the notable peasants not to initiate the revenges (AI heroes cannot yet)
 - Added configuration parameter enableOtherNobleTraitsChangeAfterNobleExecution (default value is true).
 - Added configuration parameter lordCanTryAsManyTimesToPersuadeTheNotable.If this value is false, traits of other notables will not change due another notable peasant execution in the same village.
 - Added configuration parameter lordTraitChangeWhenLordPersuedeNotableNotToRevenge
 - Added configuration parameter lordTraitChangeWhenLordPersuedeNotableToRevengePurpose of the persuasion will influence your hero traits accordingly.
 - Moved mod notable configuration and persuation starting point to - Do you deal with criminals in this village?
 - Added dialogue option to return from revenger peasant persuasion options.
 - Added configuration parameter  peasantRevengePartyWaitLordDistance. Notable peasant's party will wait for player to initiate dialogue at this distance.
 - Added configuration parameter notableWillAcceptTheBribe. Notable accept bribe with certain traits and relations with hero."/>
        <!-- Insert patch notes -->
        <Tags> 
            <!-- You can use the following tags: -->
            <!-- Type: Graphical Enhancement, Map Pack, Partial Conversion, Sound, Total Conversion, Troops, UI, Utility, Weapons and Armour -->
            <!-- Setting: Native, Antiquity, Dark Ages, Medieval, Musket Era, Modern, Sci-Fi, Fantasy, Oriental, Apocalypse, Other -->
            <!-- Game Mode: Singleplayer, Multiplayer -->
            <!-- Compatible Version: e1.9.0, v1.0.0,... The currently available versions can be found at the Steam Workshop "Browse by Tag" section -->
			<Tag Value="Native" />
            <Tag Value="Singleplayer" />
            <Tag Value="v1.1.6" />
        </Tags>
    </UpdateItem>
</Tasks>
